// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Communication is a ____________",
    answer: "process",
    options: [
      "process",
      "problem",
      "power",
      "persuasion"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What Element of Communication is the source of information or message?",
    answer: "Speaker",
    options: [
      "Message",
      "Encoding",
      "Speaker",
      "Decoding"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What Element of Communication is the information, ideas, or thoughts conveyed by the speaker in words or in actions?",
    answer: "Message",
    options: [
      "Speaker",
      "Receiver",
      "Feedback",
      "Message"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What Element of Communication is the process of converting the message into words, actions, or other forms that the speaker understands?",
    answer: "Encoding",
    options: [
      "Channel",
      "Encoding",
      "Barrier",
      "Context"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What Element of Communication the medium or the means, such as personal or non-personal, verbal or nonverbal, in which the encoded message is conveyed?",
    answer: "Channel",
    options: [
      "Message",
      "Context",
      "Channel",
      "Barrier"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What Element of Communication is the process of interpreting the encoded message of the speaker by the receiver?",
    answer: "Decoding",
    options: [
      "Decoding",
      "Receiver",
      "Feedback",
      "Encoding"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What Element of Communication is the recipient of the message, or someone who decodes the message?",
    answer: "Receiver",
    options: [
      "Speaker",
      "Message",
      "Receiver",
      "Barrier"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What Element of Communication is the reactions, responses, or information provided by the receiver?",
    answer: "Feedback",
    options: [
      "Feedback",
      "Speaker",
      "Channel",
      "Message"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What Element of Communication is the environment where Communication takes place?",
    answer: "Context",
    options: [
      "Speaker",
      "Context",
      "Channel",
      "Encoding"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What Element of Communication is the factors that affect the flow of communication?",
    answer: "Barrier",
    options: [
      "Barrier",
      "Message",
      "Feedback",
      "Channel"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "What Model of Communication is known as the Mother of all Communication Models?",
    answer: "Shannon-Weaver Model",
    options: [
      "Transaction Model",
      "Intersection Model",
      "Shannon-Weaver Model",
      "Scharmm Model"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];